http://www.jeo.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy sets out how JEO Consulting Group, Inc. uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.
JEO Consulting Group, Inc. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
JEO Consulting Group, Inc. may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. By continuing to use the Website you signify that you have read and understood this statement.
The effective date of this Privacy Policy is November 26, 2018.
What we collect
We will not collect any personal information that is not voluntarily supplied by you. We will not collect any personal information when you are browsing the website. You may be asked to provide your personal information to take certain actions. You are not required to provide the personal information that we request, but, if you choose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any inquiries you may have. We may collect a variety of information, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, demographic information, and other information that is necessary to complete that action.
What we do with the information we gather
The personal information we collect helps us understand your needs and provide you with a better service. We may use your personal information for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We will use your personal information to provide the services you request and process your transactions.
We may use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.
We may periodically contact you via your email address to tell you about new products or services, solicit feedback, or send you special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting.  If we decide to provide email offers, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of any emails by notifying us at contact@jeo.com.
From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you for market research purposes.  We may also use personal information to compile aggregated demographic information for market research, data trending, or similar uses.  The aggregated information and studies will not be linked to any personally identifiable information.
If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.
We will never sell or disclose your personal information.
Security
The security of your personal information is of utmost concern to JEO Consulting Group, Inc. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your personal information, and we take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of this information.   While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
How we use cookies
We use website browser software tools such as cookies and web server logs to gather information about your browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our website and make your visit to the website more enjoyable. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our website to better meet the needs of our users and prospective users. Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our website as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our website and evaluate our website's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture any personal information about you.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites that are not owned or controlled by JEO Consulting Group, Inc., including, but not limited to our partners, affiliates, and advertisers. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites.  We encourage you to review the privacy statement of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to our website.
Jobs at JEO
When you choose to post a resume to the careers section of the Website and apply to become part of the JEO team, please note that you will be taken to a third-party URL (https://jeoconsultinggroup.applytojob.com/apply) and these pages will be branded as JEO. The personal information you provide via the URL will be used solely for the purposes for which it is provided (including the processing of your application) and will be retained for such period as is necessary to comply with JEO’s legal and administrative requirements.
Children’s Privacy
If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to take necessary actions.
Legal Disclaimer
We may share your personal information when we believe disclosure is required by law and when we believe that the disclosure of your personal information is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.
Your ability to edit and delete your information
You may request the information you supply to us be edited or deleted by contacting us at contact@jeo.com.
©2020 JEO Consulting Group Inc. and JEO Architecture Inc.
|
Website Design & Development by UNANIMOUS
Back to Top
